<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>STA Russell Announcements</title><link>https://matthewspencesta.github.io/Daily-Announcements-RSS-Feed/rss.xml</link><description>Latest announcements from STA Russell</description><atom:link href="https://matthewspencesta.github.io/Daily-Announcements-RSS-Feed/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:42:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Today is Wednesday, February 4th, 2026.</title><link>https://sta-russell.cdsbeo.on.ca/apps/pages/DailyAnnouncements</link><description>&lt;p&gt;It is a week 1 schedule.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">a2ec0c1344aa8e0151349a9aa745474a71e91b3e20f0040a50c6bf897fc93057</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 07:42:23 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title>A message from Guidance:</title><link>https://sta-russell.cdsbeo.on.ca/apps/pages/DailyAnnouncements</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Students looking to make a course change MUST sign up for a meeting in the Guidance office. Last day for course changes is Monday, February 9th.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">ab356ce6c117a6a3658b234966d12a4b9f6c28626f6870584c4ecea6ff888f28</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 07:42:23 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title>A message from Mr. Vonesch:</title><link>https://sta-russell.cdsbeo.on.ca/apps/pages/DailyAnnouncements</link><description>&lt;p&gt;STA's annual "Shrove Tuesday Pancake Breakfast" is coming up in 2 weeks! If you need volunteer hours, or would just like to help make and serve pancakes, please see Mr. Vonesch at the chaplaincy office to sign up!&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">0e6188d879664e3c3284d37e0bc49cb99a3c46045477c540de5cdb17a2696448</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 07:42:23 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title>A message from Mme Perron and Mrs Kwok:</title><link>https://sta-russell.cdsbeo.on.ca/apps/pages/DailyAnnouncements</link><description>&lt;p&gt;There will be a mandatory unity club meeting today at lunch at 10:40 in room 127 Mrs Zurawski's room please bring your lunch. All presenters MUST attend!!!&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">c0d115edb729aa6374eaa106b02d2410f1bffa87f689b330154f53d0b3e8d7d3</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 07:42:23 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title>A message from Mme Perron:</title><link>https://sta-russell.cdsbeo.on.ca/apps/pages/DailyAnnouncements</link><description>&lt;p&gt;All Europe Trip Students are reminded to bring in any remaining items for our Clothing and gently used items fundraiser as we will be dropping items off on Friday afternoon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monday Feb 2nd&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is a week 1 schedule.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A reminder to any interested grade 10/11 students, applications for next year's service trip to Costa Rica are due tomorrow. Please see Mr. Vonesch at the chaplaincy office for details.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grad photo orders have started to arrive. If you ordered grad photos, please check in Guidance with Mrs Marcellus to pick them up. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reminder to Varsity Girls' hockey players to check Teams for important information regarding hockey this week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All online students need to report to the atrium at the beginning of their online period today to meet briefly with Ms. Timmins and Mrs. Marcellus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Students looking to make a course change MUST sign up for a meeting in the Guidance office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Attention Ravens! Interested in joining the Varsity CrossFit Team? Sign-up sheets are posted outside the gymnasium. There will be an info meeting on Tuesday, February 10 at 10:45 a.m. in the weight room. Training sessions run Tuesdays from 2:20–3:00 p.m. and our CrossFit competition is scheduled for April 2026. Come check it out!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;the Weight Room is open daily at lunch from 10:40–11:20. Thursdays are reserved for female students only. Plus, the weight room is also open Tuesday after school. Come Join Mrs. Longval for a strength, cardio or stretch session.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There will be a meeting for 7/8 boys volleyball today at 11:20 in room 148.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tuesday Feb 3rd&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is a week 1 schedule.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Students looking to make a course change MUST sign up for a meeting in the Guidance office. Last day for course changes is Monday, February 9th.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There will be a meeting today during the am break for all Web crew and 7/8 student council. The meeting will take place in Mme Plourdes classroom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ski/snowboard outing that was scheduled for Thursday Feb 12 will now take place on Wed Feb 11th. This weeks outing remains on Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Applications for next year's service trip to Costa Rica are due today. Please submit to Mr. Vonesch before the end of the day&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;STA's annual "Shrove Tuesday Pancake Breakfast" is coming up in 2 weeks! If you need volunteer hours, or would just like to help make and serve pancakes, please see Mr. Vonesch at the chaplaincy office to sign up!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow evening, STA will host RHS for our final two league games for Boys Basketball. The Juniors play at 6:30 and the Seniors, 8:00. Come out and support our Ravens Boys Basketball Teams!&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">ca84dddeb67fdaa7ad8299944440e8284e7100f238ee74f7096d0521e8138ee6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 07:42:23 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>